{
    "subject": "resource/Antony_Thachuparambil",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1963-06-09",
    "human_readable": "Antony Thachuparambil died on June 9, 1963.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8865875005722046,
            "question": "When did Antony Thachuparambil die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.798910915851593,
            "question": "What was the date of Antony Thachuparambil's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7481728196144104,
            "question": "Who was Antony Thachuparambil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6830886006355286,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the circumstances surrounding Antony Thachuparambil's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5691638588905334,
            "question": "Are there any sources that provide further details about Antony Thachuparambil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5583615303039551,
            "question": "Is there any historical context related to Antony Thachuparambil's life and death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5481293201446533,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Antony Thachuparambil's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5311341285705566,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Antony Thachuparambil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5304728150367737,
            "question": "In what year did Antony Thachuparambil pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4336753189563751,
            "question": "What field was Antony Thachuparambil known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Antony Thachuparambil died on June 9, 1963.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2069_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Antony Thachuparambil pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2069_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events associated with Antony Thachuparambil?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2069_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Antony Thachuparambil's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2069_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2069_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nReasoning:\n\n* The first document mentions Fr. Antony Thachuparambil as \"known as \u2018Missionary of Chelakkara\u2019\" and provides his date of death as June 9, 1963.\n* The third document confirms this information by stating that Antony Thachuparambil was born on December 8, 1894, and died on June 9, 1963.\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Antony Thachuparambil known as \u2018Missionary of Chelakkara\u2019... Died\\n9th June1963\" and \"Father Antony Thachuparambil had served about three decades since 1930 in Chelakkara, an extremely backward forest area. He had made immense contribution for the overall development of Chelakkara, serving all sections of society irrespective of caste, colour and religion.\\nThe priest had established a school, Balabhavan, for orphans and a church in the 1930s. Father Antony, popularly known as 'Missionary of Chelakkara', was declared Servant of God by the Vatican, June 9, 2009.\" These details support that Antony Thachuparambil died on June 9, 1963."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}